newsbiscuit.com 2018-12-25

# Privacy policyNewsBiscuit | NewsBiscuit

This privacy policy sets out how Net Loss Ltd uses and protects any information that you give Net Loss Ltd when you use this website.

Net Loss Ltd is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

Net Lost Ltd may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page periodically to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 1 September 2006.

_**What we collect**_

We may collect the following information:

  * user name

  * email address

_**What we do with the information we gather**_

We require this information to provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * Internal record keeping;

  * If you have registered for the daily email you will receive notification of new stories as they are published;

  * If you have ticked the box for ‘send me the occasional email about new features’ we may periodically send you promotional emails about new features, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting. These will be sent to the email address which you have provided;

  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you by email for market research purposes. We will only use your information in conjunction with NewsBiscuit.

_**Security**_

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

_**How we use cookies**_

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and the data is then removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. However, this may prevent you from taking full advantage of the features of the website.

_**Links to other websites**_

Our website may contain links to enable you to visit other websites of interest easily. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites, and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

Share this story...

  *
